

VU THANH NAM

Mechanical Engineer

Have worked domestically and 2 years in Japan in the mechanical field. Have been exposed to different working environments. Be eager to learn, dedicated to work. Wish to do work related to mechanical to learn and contribute to the company.

PROFILE

Date of birth: 30/04/1998

Single

• Phar

>-+- -f h:-+h: 20/04/1000

2016 - 2020

Pham Kha, Thanh Mien, Hai

EDUCATION

HANOI UNIVERSITY OF INDUSTRY

MECHANICAL ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY

2016 - 2020

Graduated with good

SKILLS

TEAMWORK SKILLS

CAN USE MECHANICAL SOFTWARE (
SOLIDWORKS, AUTO CAD,..)

CAN USE COMPUTER SOFTWARE (WORD, EXCEL, POWERPOINT,...)

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

CONG TY CO KHI QUAN VU

2022 - 2024

有限会社 テックイン

EXTRACT DRAWINGS FOR PROCESSING

Using auto cad and solidworks software to draw drawings, cut with laser machine, and process drawings

ACHINE MANAGEMENT, WORK PLAN, DIRECT MACHINE OPERATION (LASER, PRESSING MACHINE, BENDING MACHINE, LATHE, MILLING MACHINE)

Experience in reading mechanical drawings, operating mechanical machines, and managing work effectively specific job:

- Operate laser cutting machine: cutting sheet metal products
- Operate metal stamping machine: Read manufacturing drawings, Install machine adjustment molds to make shaped details,
- Check size measurement and count the quantity, Check product surface, cleaning molds and machines

CERTIFICATIONS

2018 - 2020

CAD/Solidworks Club of Hanoi University of Industry

APTIS B1

INTERESTS

Learn mechanical software design , play sports, read books, listen to music

© topcv.vn